going
yeah can imagine
this don't even joke like that [__] not
while my kids are here sorry in so
exited me sister work at the top floor
of the world center in the United States
of America on
September and I couldn't have done it
without your support bro seriously just
think of all the times my kids pooped
their diapers you were always the first
to volunteer when they needed those
things
changed man if Dad could see us now I
wonder what he would
say here we are babies say salutations
to the top of the world haha they're so
excited they can't even speak it must be
thrilling to finally be out of the house
and away from the TV screen and watching
your Gabby gab mother put on cartoons no
we're having an outing today bro can you
watch these dumb kids I'm going to move
my things into my office on
it y canot
have ch is for adult men
I'm telling you you're messing with the
wrong
guy I'm telling you this is your last
warning back
off hey Charles where did manic go you
don't know oh well I'm sure he'll turn
up
eventually what are you looking at now
son po po that appears to be another
baby in that Tower over there and he
appears to be around the same age as I
you know his name that baby is mly obes
is he
okay yes papa it's quite sexy hopefully
he's not so big he makes the building
collapse if it does at least it won't
bring down our
Tower after all what are the odds of
both Towers falling on the same day
daddy it's almost 7:00 and you still
didn't make me breakfast ah yes I'll
call B up now actually Daddy I thought
it would be nice if you made me a nice
home-cooked meal for a change how can I
make you food you dumb child we're on
the top of a building a
building because daddies who love their
sons a whole lot can do anything well
you got that
right hello Butler I would like a bed of
caviar resting on a club cracker sent up
to the topmost floor of the World Trade
Center building on the
left a club cracker what are you an
actual
Baby Daddy what would you say if I
bought you an expensive Superman
Father's Day card from wmar.com I would
say you [__] up because Father's day
was 2 months ago
h a
little a
little Charles will you just hurry up
and take the damn photo
already
it's well make it quick I got raw men in
the
microwave don't you think H oh yeah I
suppose it is getting a little close but
I doubt it's anything to worry about oh
my God
it [__] [__] damn
it Charles Charles you have to get up we
need to go now what is man who's manic
it it can't be
St you call
[__] no Charles H you hug I am not the
real George Bush I am just a product of
your imagination created because I'm
your favorite President in other words I
am your will to survive though imagine
that the real George Bush is actually
here and we will defeat El been Laden
together Mingo with this the joke how
about you shut up and do as I
say what do you mean you are not letting
anyone through America is under attack
it's to dangerous the stairs below are
cliping you will never make it but my
babies this isn't just about you Dum
[__] don't you see that the whole
country is in tears right now what about
the other civilians with their own kids
America is under attack and all you can
think about is saving yourself oh man
[__] all that noise the Hedgehog royal
family will survive this
day don't worry babies I'll call your
dad he'll know just what to do honey
it's me we're not going to believe the
crazy day at work I'm having
[Music]
oh you're watching it on the news that's
well can you come pick us up no what do
you mean no I'm your [__]
wife oh so this is Revenge for last
week I did
not we'll discuss that later are you
going to come save your family's life or
not well then I'm hanging
up love you too okay sonyia new plan I'm
going to tie this rope around you and
I'm going to throw you like a football
into that event up there do you know
what a football
is well you are about to become
[Music]
one daddy the plane just hit the other
Tower daddy daddy where are you
I'm three floors down son what why
aren't you up here protecting me like a
good daddy you have big muscles it's not
like you can get
Hur you all right Papa but my heart
can and that kids is how your uncle and
I escaped 911 you're so cool mama I call
[__] and what do you mean I got
thrown out the window never to be seen
again there's way to many holes in your
story for it to be believable Mama well
manic I knew you wouldn't believe me so
I called in a guy you would believe you
could even call him the guy George
Bush oh my God it's Elijah Wood from
Spike 3D I love that movie hey me too
because I was in it you know what I also
love 911 because I was there too and you
know what I hate wi in so type a squad
and shut up because the guy is here no
offense Elijah would but what do you
have to do with 9/11 how the F should I
know no you were there that's why I
called you here oh yet I forgot my
current days kind of blur together now
after finishing the legendary Trilogy of
Lord of the Rings because I haven't had
a roll as iconic as mother [__] fro
bag anyway there I was October 11th of
2001 hey can I get a hot dog that
depends you got $2 that depends you
going to suck my balls no no money no
hot dog do you know who I am froo bagin
no I'm the guy the best video game
player of all time I know you P me every
day trying to get free hot dogs but it
doesn't matter you still have to pay the
same as everybody else well I don't want
to pay then you can go [__]
yourself no you can go [__] yourself you
know what I don't want to buy one of
your hot dogs you're a
[__] sweet nibblets a plane just hit
the Twin Towers this is your lucky dhar
cheeks I got to go do some epic Heroes
[Music]
sit don't worry green baby I'm here to
rescue you come to
[Music]
pop Washton Square we're trying to bring
him on the air that was a second plane
that just
[Music]
blew tired of being what you want me to
be feeling so faithless lost under the
surface
don't know what you're expecting of me
but under the pressure of walking in
your Sho CAU in the undertoe just CAU in
the under toe every step that I take is
another mistake to you caught in the
under toe just caught in the under
toe I become so num I can't feel you
there become so ti so much for where I'm
becoming